Finding Aid for the Barbara and Willard Morgan photographs and papers LSC.2278
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 9: Barbara Morgan photographic material, 1920s-2000s; Negative numbers are written on many of the photographic prints and contact prints. Some prints are signed, stamped, or have labels crediting Barbara Morgan. Many unmounted prints have notations on the back, such as numbers or the lowerc
  - Subseries 9.2: Dance photography, 1920s-1990s, undated; 1930s-1940s
    - Martha Graham - photographic prints (contact prints), 1930s-1940s
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1940; 4 x 5 contact prints. Also includes contact prints with image dimensions 2-3/8 x 2-5/8 in. (60mm x 70mm). (Box 293)
        Rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham including Every Soul is a Circus and Frontier.
        Dancers include Martha Graham, Erick Hawkins, Merce Cunningham, and other Graham dancers.
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1945; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 291)
        Martha Graham and Group in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham including American Document, American Provincials, Chronicle, Columbiad (Graham solo), and Deaths and Entrances.
        Dancers include Martha Graham, Erick Hawkins, Sophie Maslow, Frieda Flier, Jean Erdman, Jane Dudley, and other dancers in the Martha Graham Company.
      - Graham and Group, 1937-1939, undated; 5 x 7 contact prints. (Box 428)
        Martha Graham (solo); with Cunningham, Hawkins, and Graham Group; Hawkins (solo); and casual studio photography, including:
        Graham (solo) in American Document: Indian Solo, Columbiad, Immediate Tragedy (1937), Letter to the World (Swirl), and Sarabande
        Graham with Cunningham and Hawkins Every Soul is a Circus, and Puritan Love Duet
        Erick Hawkins solo in American Document
        Erick Hawkins with Douglas Morgan and others in studio shots for fun.
      - Graham and Group, 1938, undated; 5 x 7 and smaller contact prints. (Box 429)
        Martha Graham (solo), with Erick Hawkins, and with Merce Cunningham, including:
        Graham (solo) in Deep Song, Satyric Festival, Ekstatis, and Indian Ancestor
        Graham with Erick Hawkins in Every Soul is a Circus and Puritan Love Duet
        Graham with Merce Cunningham in Every Soul is a Circus
      - Graham and Group, circa 1938, undated.; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 297)
        Merce Cunningham, Jean Erdman, and Graham Group, including unidentified Graham dancers demonstrating Graham technique.
        Also includes Martha Graham with Erick Hawkins, and 2" x 3" prints of Martha Graham in unidentified dance.
      - Graham and Group, Graham with Cunningham and Hawkins, and Graham portraits, undated; 5 x 7 and smaller contact prints. (Box 305, Box 423)
        Martha Graham, Merce Cunningham, and Erick Hawkins, including:
        Martha Graham in Sarabande, El Penitente, Ekstasis, Imperial Gesture, Every Soul is a Circus, Letter to the World, American Episode, Indian Episode, Punch and Judy, Harlequinade, Lamentation, Primitive Mysteries, and Deep Song
        Graham with Cunningham and Hawkins in Deaths and Entrances
        Graham with Hawkins in Puritan Love Duet
        Martha Graham in black dress with organdy collar
        Also includes Graham and Group at Bennington College.
        Also includes Celebration postcard.
      - Graham and Group, Bennington College Festival, 1935-1939, undated.; 4 x 5 and smaller contact prints. (Box 434)
        Martha Graham and Group in Frontier, Lamentation, Every Soul is a Circus, Primitive Mysteries, Deep Song, American Document: Puritan Love Duet with Erick Hawkins, Declaration, Emancipation Episode, Letter to the World, El Penitente.
        Also includes Graham technique demonstration outdoors.
      - Graham and Group and other dancers at Bennington College in 1938 (Box 305)
        Martha Graham and Group, Graham casual backstage, Graham and students candid, candid other, Graham technique outdoors, Erick Hawkins, Ethel Butler directing Graham rehearsal.
      - Graham and Group, Hanya Holm and Group at Bennington College, 1938, undated.; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 433)
        Graham works include World's Fair Preview (Graham and other dancers), Graham rehearsal World's Fair 1938, and O'Donnell on Roof. Hanya Holm works include Want Ads, Trend (Solo), Trend (ensemble), and Rehearsal Bennington 1938.
        Other dancers include Folk Dancers, Music Preview, Gretel Whalen, Olin Downs, and rehearsal.
      - Graham and Group, May O'Donnell and others: 1938 World's Fair, Bennington College, and Sarah Lawrence College, 1938-1957.; 4 x 5 negatives and contact prints. (Box 435)
        Graham and Group, May O'Donnell and other dancers, musicians and New York political figures at the 1938 World's Fair, Bennington College, and Sarah Lawrence College photographic work.
        Bennington College dancers also include Hanya Holm in Trend, Want Ads, and Improvisation.
        Sarah Lawrence College includes fencing, buildings, jazz musician Martin Gornley, Doris Riker, and students in various venues and activities.
      - Graham, Cunningham, Hawkins, Humphrey, and Weidman, 1938-1944, undated.; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 304)
        Photomontage of Martha Graham, Doris Humphrey, Charles Weidman, Erick Hawkins and Merce Cunningham.
      - Martha Graham and Erick Hawkins, 1935-1940.; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 294)
        Martha Graham and Erick Hawkins in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham including Frontier, Harlequinade, Imperial Gesture, Immediate Tragedy, Lamentation, and Letter to the World.
        Most of the photographs in this box are of Martha Graham alone.
        Letter to the World photographs also include Erick Hawkins.
      - Martha Graham, Erick Hawkins, and Graham Group, 1938-1939; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 290)
        Rehearsals and demonstrations of American Document choreographed by Martha Graham in the Graham Studio NYC and at Bennington College.
        Also includes non-dance photographs of Graham and Eric Hawkins at Bennington College, and Erick Hawkins in Striding Figure, 1939.
    - Martha Graham - negatives, 1920s-1940s
      Subseries 9.8 Cut film (4 x 5 format and smaller) negatives and contact prints, 1920s-1970s, undated; and Subseries 9.8 Cut film (5 x 7 format and smaller) negatives and contact prints, 1920s-1970s, undated, contain many additional boxes of negatives of Martha Graham and Graham Group.
      For detailed descriptions of Martha Graham and Graham Group negatives, including names of dances and dancers, see Subseries 9.8.
      Boxes 607 and 608 are a mix of series, including some folders containing negatives of Martha Graham and Group.
      - Martha Graham portraits, 1935-1938; 4 x 5 and smaller negatives. (Box 563)
        Early portraits of Martha Graham: Immediate Tragedy, wearing organdy collar dress, kimono, rope trim dress, abstract background.
      - Martha Graham, 1932-1942, undated; Color negatives. (Box 554)
        Graham, Humphrey and Hawkins.
      - Martha Graham (solo), and Graham family, 1900-1920s; 5 x 7 and smaller negatives. (Box 549)
        Young Martha Graham and Graham family. Includes East Indian Poem, Javanese Dance, Tocsin, and copy negatives of Indian Snake Dance.
      - Martha Graham (solo), Frontier and Lamentation, 1935-1945; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 556, Folders 1-2)
        Folder 1 also includes negatives and contact prints that Deba Patnaik set aside for his Icons of Dance, and cover design for Martha Graham: Sixteen Dances in Photographic Sequences by Barbara Morgan.
        Folder 2 also includes original negatives of Martha Graham in Deep Song (some double exposure), and one color negative of Graham.
      - Martha Graham (solo), Imperial Gesture, 1935; 4 x 5 format negative, masked for publication. (Box 607)
      - Martha Graham (solo), Letter to the World (Kick), and with Erick Hawkins, 1940, undated; Includes large negatives of Letter to the World (Kick), and color negatives of Martha Graham and Erick Hawkins. (Box 595)
      - Martha Graham (solo), Letter to the World (Swirl), 1940; 2 copy negatives. (Box 607)
      - Martha Graham (solo), and with Erick Hawkins, 1933-1947, undated; 5 x 7 and smaller negatives. (Box 550)
        Martha Graham in Sarabande, Letter to the World (Swirl), and with Erick Hawkins.
      - Martha Graham (solo), with Erick Hawkins, and Louis Horst, 1931-1939; 5 x 7 and smaller negatives. (Box 551)
        Graham solos in American Document--Emancipation and Indian Ancestor, and with Erick Hawkins in Puritan Love Duet; and Louis Horst at piano.
        Also includes dance props, instruments, programs and musical scores for Deep Song and Primitive Mysteries.
      - Graham and Group, 1914-1940; 4 x 5 negatives (Box 455)
        Martha Graham and Group in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham primarily dated 1938 and 1939 including the dances Chronicle, Spectre (Red Skirt) 1914, Steps in the Street, Prelude to Action, Columbiad (solo), Deaths and Entrances, Deep Song, Ekstasis, and El Penitente. Dancers noted on negative sleeves include Martha Graham, Graham Group, May O'Donnell, Erick Hawkins, Pearl Lang, and Merce Cunningham.
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1939; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 454)
        Martha Graham and Group in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for the work American Document choreographed by Martha Graham primarily dated 1938 and 1939 including the dances Puritan Love Duet with Erick Hawkins; Emancipation Episode (solo and duet); group demonstration/rehearsal of American Document and casuals afterward at Graham Studio NYC, including dancers Martha Graham, Sophie Maslow, Freida Flier, and Marjoie Mazia, with casuals and dressing room photographs additionally including Housley, Louis Horst and Erick Hawkins.
        Bennington College summer 1938: American Document--Crossfire; Indian Episode; Declaration with Erick Hawkins, May O'Donnell and group; Erick Hawkins solos in Song of Songs and One Man, and Puritan Episode; and Three Women including dancers Sophie Maslow, Frieda Flier, Jane Dudley and Jane Erdman.
        Also includes American Provincials dated 1935--Act of Piety, Act of Judgement; and Celebration with dancers Jane Dudley, Sophie Maslow and Frieda Flier dated 1937.
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1940; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 456)
        Martha Graham and Group in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham including the dances El Penitente, Every Soul Is a Circus, and Frontier. Dancers noted on negative sleeves include Martha Graham, Erick Hawkins, Merce Cunningham, Jean Erdman, Nelle Fisher, Sophie Maslow, Ethel Butler, Frieda Flier, and Marjorie Mazia.
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1940; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 457)
        Martha Graham and Group in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham including the dances Harlequinade, Imperial Gesture, Immediate Tragedy, Lamentation, Letter to the World, and Primitive Canticles. Dancers noted on negative sleeves include Martha Graham and Erick Hawkins.
        This box also includes double exposure prints of Martha Graham in Lamentation, Letter to the World (Kick) and Letter to the World (Swirl).
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1940; 5 x 7 and smaller negatives. (Box 552)
        Graham in Columbiad, Deaths and Entrances, Ekstasis solo and with Erick Hawkins in studio photographs, American Document, Letter to the World, and Every Soul is a Circus; Graham Group in Primitive Mysteries, and Graham Group dancers Nelle Fisher, Frieda Flier, and Marjorie Mazie.
      - Graham and Group, 1935-1940; 8 x 10 prints and master negatives. (Box 608)
        Letter to the World (Kick) and Letter to the World (Swirl), American Document, Frontier, Every Soul is a Circus, and Deep Song.
        Also includes 8 x 10 negatives of experimental photography, photomontages and rayograms, including some Graham dance double exposure.
      - Graham and Group, 1938-1957; 4 x 5 negatives and contact prints. (Box 435)
        Martha Graham and Group, May O'Donnell and other dancers, musicians and New York political figures at the 1938 World's Fair, Bennington College, and Sarah Lawrence College photographic work.
        Bennington College dancers also include Hanya Holm in Trend, Want Ads, and Improvisation; Sarah Lawrence College includes fencing, buildings, jazz musician Martin Gornley, Doris Riker, and students in various venues and activities.
      - Graham and Group, World's Fair, 1938-1939; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 562)
        Rehearsals, Graham solo, May O'Donnell. Also includes World's Fair personalities.
      - Graham and Group, Bennington College, Graham and Hawkins, circa 1925-1938, undated; 5 x 7 negatives, 35mm transparencies, and 4 x 5 and 8 x 10 copy negatives from reproduction files. (Box 558)
        Dance photographs of Martha Graham and Group 1938 in Indian American Document, Bennington: Graham and Hawkins, Louis Horst, and Primitive Mysteries. Also includes copy negatives of Barbara Morgan experimental and dance photographs
      - Graham and Group, Bennington College, 1935-1939, undated; 4 x 5 and smaller negatives. (Box 434, Box 563)
        4 x 5 negatives of Graham and Group at Bennington College Festival:
        Box 434 - Martha Graham and Group in Frontier, Lamentation, Every Soul is a Circus, Primitive Mysteries, Deep Song, American Document: Puritan Love Duet with Erick Hawkins, Declaration, Emancipation Episode, Letter to the World, El Penitente. Rehearsals including Sophie Maslow, Jane Dudley and Valerie Bettis. Also includes Martha Graham technique demonstration outdoors.
        Box 563 - Graham, Hawkins and Group: American Document, and casuals.
      - Graham and Group, Bennington College, 1935-1942; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 458)
        Martha Graham and Group in rehearsals and studio photography sessions for works choreographed by Martha Graham including the dances Primitive Mysteries--Hymn to the Virgin, Crucifixus, and Hosanna, Punch and Judy, Sarabande, Satyric Festival, War Theme, and Martha Graham technique demonstrated by Dorothy Bird, May O'Donnell and Ethel Bird at Bennington College in the summer of 1938.
        Dancers noted on negative sleeves include Martha Graham, Erick Hawkins, Group trio, Jean Erdman, Jane Dudley, and Ethel Butler.
        This box also includes portraits of Martha Graham wearing a striped dress and Martha Graham's signature.
    - Graham technique - photographic prints and contact prints, 1930s-1940s, 1990s
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Merce Cunningham, Ethel Butler, Jean Erdman, and Nina Caiserman, 1930s-1990s. Vintage (1930s-1940s); 8 x 10 prints, contact prints, and 8 x 10 reproduction prints, 1990s. (Box 241)
        Also includes 8 x 10 and smaller prints of Martha Graham and Graham Group in American Document, American Provincials, Deaths and Entrances, Deep Song, and Every Soul is a Circus, a print of Jane Dudley, Sophie Maslow, and Frieda Flier in Celebration, and Martha Graham in Chronicle.
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Dorothy Bird, May O'Donnell, Ethel Butler, and Nina Caiserman, circa 1894-1941; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 296)
      - Graham technique demonstration, circa 1938, undated.; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 297)
        Martha Graham dancers (Merce Cunningham, Jean Erdman, some group, and some unidentified Graham dancers) demonstrating Graham technique.
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Merce Cunningham and by Ethel Butler, and Graham technique outdoors at Bennington College, 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 305)
      - Graham technique demonstrated outdoors at Bennington College, 1935-1939, undated.; 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 434)
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Merce Cunningham, Frances Sunstein and other Graham dancers, 1941, undated.; 11 x 14 format prints and 8 panels of 4 x 5 contact prints. (Box 441)
    - Graham technique - negatives, circa 1930s-1940s
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Dorothy Bird, May O'Donnell and Ethel Bird at Bennington College, 1938; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 458)
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Ethel Butler, Nina Caiserman, Merce Cunningham, Jean Erdman, and group, 1939-1942.; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 459)
        This box also contains unidentified and unnumbered negatives, possibly including Letter to the World and Columbiad.
      - Graham technique demonstrated by Graham Group, and Martha Graham (solo), 1935-1945; 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 556, Folders 1-2)
        Folder 1 also includes negatives and contact prints that Deba Patnaik set aside for his book, Icons of Dance, and Martha Graham in Frontier and Lamentation.
        Folder 2 also includes original negatives of Martha Graham in Deep Song, some double exposure.
    - Other dancers - photographic prints (large), 1930s-1940s
      Martha Graham photographs in this series also include images of "other dancers" who danced with Martha Graham Group. Most of the photographic prints in these files are gelatin silver.
      - Valerie Bettis - Desperate Heart (Photomontage I), 1944, printed 1972; Signed. Print is trimmed to 15-1/4 x 19-1/4 inches and mounted on 22 x 28 inch board. (Box 392)
      - Valerie Bettis - Kick (white dress, back of feet), 11 x 14 format print matted to 20 x 24 inches with 10-1/2 x 13-1/2 inch window. (Box 388)
      - Valerie Bettis - Desperate Heart (Kick) (high kick, face not seen), 1944, archivally printed 1973; Signed. Print is trimmed to 19-5/8 x 15-3/8 inches and mounted on 28 x 22 inch board. (Box 392)
      - Humphrey-Weidman, 8 x 10 format prints matted on large foamcore boards. (Box 448)
      - Humphrey-Weidman (photomontage), Print trimmed to 12-1/2 x 10-1/2 inches mounted on 17 x 19 inch board. (Box 383)
      - May O'Donnell - Cornerstone, 1945; Print is signed, and trimmed to 19 x 13-3/4 inches, mounted on 27-5/8" x 20 inch board. Water damage to board. (Box 388)
    - Other dancers - photographic prints (medium), 1930s-1940s
      1939-1944. Medium-sized prints of dancers are mostly 11 x 14 and 16 x 20 format loose prints (unmatted and unmounted). Some are smaller prints, various sizes, mounted or matted to 16 x 20 inches. Many are signed.
      - Valerie Bettis - Desperate Heart--solo, and Kick (front), 11 x 14 format prints (3 prints). (Box 332)
      - Valerie Bettis - Desperate Heart--solo (double exposure), Kick (back) and Kick (front), 16 x 20 format prints. (Box 365)
      - Valerie Bettis - Desperate Heart--solo, Kick, and double exposure, 16 x 20 format prints (2 matted, 9 unmatted). (Box 368)
      - Valerie Bettis - Desperate Heart--solo, 16 x 20 format prints (3 prints). (Box 374)
      - Valerie Bettis - Solo, 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 11 x 14 format print. (FMD 30) (Box 338)
      - Si Lan Chen, 16 x 20 format prints. (Print in Box 368 is matted). (Box 365, Box 368)
      - Merce Cunningham - Root of the Unfocus, and Totem Ancestor, 1942-1944.; 11 x 14 format prints (4 prints). (Box 332)
      - Merce Cunningham - Root of the Unfocus (double exposure), and Totem Ancestor (leap), 1942; 16 x 20 format prints. Totem Ancestor (leap) and Cunningham with Pearl Lang prints are mounted. (Box 368)
      - Merce Cunningham - Root of the Unfocus, and Totem Ancestor, Leap, 1942-1944.; 16 x 20 format prints. 3 prints, including 2 double exposure. (Box 365)
      - Merce Cunningham - Totem Ancestor, 16 x 20 format prints. (Box 359)
      - Merce Cunningham - (double exposure), 1944; 11 x 14 format print matted to 16 x 20 inches with 7" x 8-3/4" mat window. (Box 369)
      - Merce Cunningham and Pearl Lang - (double exposure), and Leap, 16 x 20 format prints. (Box 359)
      - Merce Cunningham and Pearl Lang - (double exposure), and Leap, undated; 11 x 14 format prints. 10 prints of double exposure, 1 print of Leap. (Box 333)
      - Merce Cunningham and Pearl Lang - (double exposure), and Leap, 1942; 11 x 14 format prints. (Box 359)
        Multiple prints of each photograph.
      - Merce Cunningham with Pearl Lang, 1942; 16 x 20 format print, mounted. (Box 368)
      - Asadata Dafora - [Drummer], undated; 11 x 14 format print. (Box 333)
      - Asadata Dafora, 1941; Print trimmed to 13" x 10" and mounted on 16 x 20 in. board. (Box 369)
      - Asadata Dafora and unidentified dancer, undated; Print matted to 16 x 20 inches with 13" x 7-3/8" mat window. (Box 369)
      - Asadata Dafora, undated.; 16 x 20 format print. (Box 371)
      - Jane Dudley, undated.; 16 x 20 format print. (Box 371)
      - Erick Hawkins - Liberty Tree, undated.; 11 x 14 format prints. (Box 333)
      - Erick Hawkins - (torso), 1940.; Print trimmed to 11" x 10", mounted on 16 x 20 in. board (Box 369)
      - Erick Hawkins - Yankee Doodle, Insubstantial Pageant, and [Searching] (photomontage), 1940, printed 1979; 16 x 20 format prints. (Box 371)
      - Hanya Holm--solo, portrait, and Holm Group, including Bennington, 1938.; 11 x 14 format prints (Box 333)
      - Hanya Holm, solo, undated.; 11 x 14 format prints. (Box 334)
      - Hanya Holm--solo, undated.; 16 x 20 format print. (Box 372)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Lynchtown, Rehearsal Nightmare (double exposure), Square Dance, Inquest, and Weidman--solo, [On My Mother's Side], 1938, undated. (Box 335)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Lynchtown, ca. 1938, undated.; 16 x 20 format prints (7 prints). (Box 366)
        Also includes one double exposure and other photographs.
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Lynchtown and Opus 51, 1938.; Opus 51, 1938 (Bennington), is an 8 x 10 format print matted to 16 x 20 in board. Lynchtown print is trimmed to 9-3/4" x 13-1/2" mounted on 16 x 20 in. board. (Box 371)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Lynchtown, 1938.; 3 prints, trimmed and mounted on 16 x 20 in. boards. (Box 372)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Lynchtown (Group) and Weidman solo--On My Mother's Side, 1938-1940.; 16 x 20 format prints. (Box 362)
        Lynchtown includes Group and solo photographs of Bea Seckler.
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Passacaglia, Shakers, and With My Red Fires, 1938, undated.; 11 x 14 format prints (6 prints). (Box 334)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Passacaglia, Square Dance, and [Untitled], 1938, undated.; 16 x 20 format prints (5 prints). (Box 378)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Shakers (Humphrey Group), 1938.; 16 x 20 format prints (7 prints). (Box 377)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Shakers, Square Dance, Humphrey Group, and Humphrey and Weidman, 1938; 16 x 20 format prints. (Box 381)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Square Dance for Moderns, and With My Red Fires, 1938.; 16 x 20 format prints (7 prints). (Box 375)
      - Doris Humphrey and/or Charles Weidman - Square Dance, and Charles Weidman--solo, undated.; 16 x 20 format prints (5 prints). (Box 380)
      - Doris Humphrey--solo, undated.; 16 x 20 format prints (2 prints). (Box 374)
      - Doris Humphrey--solo, Passacaglia, 16 x 20 format print. (Box 362)
      - Doris Humphrey--solo, Passacaglia, and To the Dance, Prints mounted on 16 x 20 boards. (Box 361)
      - Louise Kloepper, 1938; 2 prints, trimmed to 13-1/2" x 10-7/8" mounted on 16 x 20 in. boards. (Box 369)
      - José Limón - Chaconne, Cowboy Song (double exposure), Mexican Suite, 1944, undated; 16 x 20 loose prints (3 prints), and prints trimmed and mounted on 16 x 20 in. boards (2 prints). (Box 354)
      - José Limón - Chaconne and Mexican Suite, 16 x 20 format prints, (2 prints). (Box 359)
      - José Limón - Cowboy Song (double exposure), José Limón, and Mexican Suite (Indian), 1944 (Box 356)